<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NPSC \'18</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="aboutEvent">The National Power Systems Conference (NPSC) has been India\'s premier conference in the area of power engineering since 1981. It is a biennial conference providing a platform for researchers and engineers from Academia,Industry and Utility to exchange their ideas, and experiences. The event is an excellent opportunity for fostering academic and industrial collaborations. The “20th National Power Systems Conference- NPSC 2018 ” will be organized by the Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, National Institute of Technology, Tiruchirappalli, Tamilnadu, India during 14th-16th December 2018.\n\n

With the theme of \“Towards a sustainable energy future through efficient, smart and green technologies\”, NPSC 2018 is anticipated to be an engaging journey to bring out new perceptions in the realm of state of art in power engineering for a sustainable energy future.\n
    </string>
    <string name="aboutUs">Started in the year 1964, the Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, offers one undergraduate programme, two postgraduate programmes (Power Systems and Power Electronics) and research degrees (M.S. and Ph.D.) in various fields of electrical and electronic engineering. The Department is recognized for leadership in research, teaching and service to the profession.</string>
    <string name="aboutVenue">The National Institute of Technology (formerly known as Regional Engineering College) Tiruchirappalli, was started as a joint and co- operative venture of the Govt. of India and the Govt. of Tamil Nadu during 1964 to cater to the needs of technical man-power in this region of the country. The College has subsequently been conferred with autonomy in financial and administrative matters to achieve rapid development. The institute was granted Deemed University Status with the approval of the UGC, the AICTE and the Govt. of India in the year 2003 and was renamed as National Institute of Technology, Tiruchirappalli (NIT Trichy). Today, NIT Trichy has emerged as one of the leading institutions in the field of technical education with excellence in academics, research, industry connect, social engagement and financial management. Ranked by NIRF 2017 as one among the top 50 institutions, occupying the 11 th position under technical institutions, NIT Trichy leads the rankings among 31 NITs in the country. At the regional level, NIT Trichy also features in the top 250 positions in QS Asia Rankings 2018. Today, NIT Trichy, offers 10 undergraduate and 27 postgraduate programs and research degrees. A salubrious campus with excellent academic departments, dedicated teachers and cream of the country among students drawn from most of the states render the institute to be the dream destination for students and teachers from far and wide.</string>
</resources>
